Look at that. Oh, my God.
White, what's going on?
Where am I supposed to aim with this thing?
I don't know.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, everyone. This is Sunao Hatake.
I'm Sunao Hatake.
I'm here at Surplus Yokohama Playtown.
I'm here.
Can you see me?
I'm here today.
There are a lot of crane games
I'd like to play.
Okay, let's get started.
Let's go.
Let's start from here.
I'll go around.
Oh!
Stuffed animals! So cute! It's so big!
It's so big, I don't know where to look.
I found a Pokemon.
So cute!
I want to get a Pokemon.
Wampachi is so cute, I want to get it
Let's get a Wampachi
Let's see...
I'd like to do a copy.
Where's the copy machine?
Oh, there it is. There it is.
Copy that.
Here it is.
Okay, I've got 1,000 yen exchanged for now.
I'll try this form.
Let's try it.
Oh, this is the pattern.
Is my head heavy?Wow, you must have a heavy head.
Surprisingly good?
Oh! Can I get this?
Will I get stuck? This one.
I saw a video that said it's good to stick stuffed animals.
I saw a video of it.
Oh, but I think I can do it.
That's a tough one!
Oh, it stood up.
He got up.
So far, so good.
He's so cute.
Oh, it's so hard!
I'm sure I'm going to spend 1,000 yen on this last one.
I'm going to stop.
I want to try the other ones.
I want to go for it.
But I don't know where to aim
I don't know.
Can't you do it?
Oh, it's hard.
It's a little difficult.
But I've always wanted to try figurines.
Figures always give me a hard time.
Oh, I have so many!
It's amazing!
Blade of Demon's Destruction
There's also a Hiroaka!
Shiraki is so cool!
What's this?
There's one like this too!
I've never seen this before!
This is my favorite Miku Hatsune!
This Miku is so cute!
I'm going to take a shot of Miku!
I've never been able to get a good shot of a figure.I've never been able to get the figures right.
I'll see if I can shift it once.
It's lifting.
Oh, that's what it feels like.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised it lifted.
I'm gonna try to get the back side.
Oh, shit, I'm stuck.
I think I might be stuck.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't know how to get out of this right now.
I'll open the door.
May I?
I'm gonna take the left claw and go for the front.
Or I'll go for the back one with the right claw.
If you could come to the side, that would be great.
Okay, thank you.
Let's go for the front.
That'll work, right? It worked, didn't it?
Oh, wait. One more time. One more time. One more time.
One more time. That was pretty good.
It's working. It's working. It's working.
That's pretty good, isn't it?
Pretty good, isn't it?
What's going on back there?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I'm back.
You're back.
We're going back.
I don't know if I can do it.
It's so hard! Oh, no!
It's gone.
I'm a little out of control.
I think I'll try some sweets for a change!
Let's go make some snacks!
Where's the candy?Where's the candy?
Oh, my God!
There's so much candy!
Jagabing sounds delicious.
Let's give it a try!
I wonder how to get the sweets.
It's pretty bold!
I was surprised at how bold it was.
You go all out, don't you?
Let's go for the candy!
Oh, I got it!
I got it for 200 yen!
I didn't know we could get candy!
I'd like to make a lot of snacks.
I want a baby animal.
Does it have a flavor?
I want a chocolate biscuit.
I want the one in the front.
It's so slow!
This crane is so cute!
The width is small.
Ehhhh...
Wait a minute.
I got it!
I got it for 100 yen!
Yay!
I got a baby animal!
I've been thinking about this since I came in here.
There's one thing I've been wondering about.
Look.
Look at this.
Oh, my God.
There are so many cranes on this thing.
You see?
This one.This.
Just move it like normal.
Oh, my God.
Look at that.
Let's go take a look.
There's so much stuff.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
It really does taste the same.
Fortune-telling?
You know what I mean?
I have a prediction.
It's the number of units you take.
I just did my first one.
Four.
I'm a bonjin.
I'd like to go over Bon-Chin.
I didn't expect it to come off.
But I got it.
I want to go over the Bon-Chin.
I didn't know it was so hard to get.
Let's go around here.
Oh, there it is!
Surprisingly, I got it.
Wait, I can't see anything but the same future.
I can only see the same future.
One, two.
Three. Four.
Oh, five.
Five.
I went there, so...
Oh, I went to the main one.
Almost pretty good.
He asked me if I had a chance.
They told me.
I'm so happy!Yay, I'm so happy!
You know what?
There's something a little different about this place.
This is it?
Wait, what is it?
What's going on?
Can we come in?
Excuse me.
Oh, my gosh!
What a surprise!
What's this?
I heard they're going to give us some kind of support.
I heard they're going to do something for me.
I'm so surprised!
I'm so, so, so, so, so surprised!
Se-no
You're amazing
It's okay, it's okay.
It's our weather
Sweep us off our feet
Wow.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Surprise.
Oh, my God.
That was shocking.
That's amazing.
This is the last of the money.
Oh, my God.
Panda!
There's a panda!There's a man in here.
This is Mendoko, isn't it?
There's a Mendoko here.
He's cute.
I want this.
Mendoko!
I love Mendoko, don't you?
He's so cute when he's catching them.
I think I can do it somehow.
I want to bring home some kind of stuffed animal.
It looks heavy.
I've been falling down the same way since a while ago.
Oh, it's so hard!
Oh, but it's coming closer and closer.
Oh, it's getting away from me
Oh, it's rolling.
Is there a trick to this?
You're trying to draw them in?
You call it a strategy?
I guess it didn't really work.
I want to get it.
How hard can it be?
It's a little heavy for my taste.
Ha-ha-ha...
I keep going back and forth between seeming to be able to do it and not being able to do it.
Oh, no, this is the last one.
Oh, no!
Wait a minute.
Wait. Why?
What?
This one's in, too.
Oh, my God.
It's a miracle.
Oh, my God.Surprise!
So this time
I visited Yokohama Play Town with this cert.
I played a lot of crane games.
I felt like a boy
I had a lot of fun!
Thank you very much!
Please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Thanks a lot!
Please subscribe!